Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- General file by SUBJECTS in boxes 63-68
  - General file by SUBJECT Co - Sp in folders with headings, 1945-62
    - LOS ANGELES CITY AFFAIRS H R 2892 2720 3238 7782 SB 859 P B 21 Public Law 352 889, 1956 '54
      Armory Elysian Park Heigts, airpollution, dispersal of industrial plants military contracts, drainage condit ons, Civil Defence Program, L A Appraisers store, L A offices of Federal Government, manufacturing employment, Passport office in LA earea, public housing program, report childrens Court of concilation, sea-Air rescue facilities L A international airport, surplus property program.
    - LOS ANGELS COUNTY AFFAIRS S 2938 3115, 1948- 55
      Air pollution abatment under federal income tax laws, ammonia plants, construction rapid transit system LA county, defense, Death Vally monument, Fallbrooks public utility district, flood hazards report L A erea, Isabella dam recreation lake, LA international airportm report motor vehicles airpollution, report watershed fire council of Southen Calif., smog problem, Whittier narrows dam.
    - LOS ANGELS COUNTY AFFAIRS H R 3222 S B 1004 S J RES [UNK] Public Law 152, 1955 '56 '57 '59
      Additional forest fire protection in California's national forests, Beale airforce base retention, denuded watersheds, demonstration plants for conversion of seawater hospitals, insular affairs committee, KLM royal dutch airline permit operating at LA airport, [UNK] trymen small livestock emergency disaster relief, surplus property program.
    - LOS ANGELES HARBOR, 1945 '44
      Development L A Long Beach harbors, Count of L A directory of importers, tide submerged lands.
    - LOS ANGELES HOUSING, 1948 '49 '50 '51 '52
      Housing shortage, low rent public housing program
    - LOS ANGELES WORLD FAIR, 1958
    - MEMBERSHIP LISTS, 1953
      Crenshaw chamber of commerce, home builders institute.
    - MEXICAN -AMERICAN AFFAIRS, 1949
      Immigration officers
    - MEXICAN -AMERICAN CLAIM COMMISSION, 1947 '48
      Rancho Tijuna claim
    - GENERAL MONCADO HR 2887 2888, 1956 '54
      Filipino crusaders world army, General Mrs Moncado, relief of them, report to committee on un- filipino activities by Gen. Moncado.
    - KNEZEVICH, John, 1951
      Ante Pavelich, loan to Yougoslavia, review of events in Yougoslavia, Ustashi organisation
    - KOREA Pre-war post-war estimated of economic position., 1951
    - LATTIMORE Oppheimer HR 8043, 1961
      Security risks
    - MORAL RE-ARMAMENT, 1955 '58 '61
      Plays: the crowning experiece, tide of history, vanishin islands.
    - MOTION PICTURE LISTS, 1949
      Government agencies contractors for motion pictures
    - NAVY DEPT AFFAIRS, 1958
      California Maritime Academy, candidates regular naval reserve officers training corps.
    - NEGRO AFFAIRS H R 314 7072 H RES 364 public Law, 1949 '51 '52 '56 '57
      APCANS [UNK], bombing Negro homes in L A, 610 [UNK] Washington halfdollar coin, constructing public housing L A, integration, National association for advancement of coloured [UNK] pamplet the racial issue, olympic freeway proposal, Powell amendment to school aid bill, tax exemption educational philantropic foundation, veterans hospital at birth place B T Washington.
    - NEW CITIZENS, 1960 ' 61
      lists
    - NEWSPAPER LISTS for McDoungh releases
    - NEWSPAPERS names addresses
    - NIXON AFFAIRS telegram sent to National National Committee
    - OLYMPIC GAMES MELBOURNE, 1956
    - SPECIAL KOREAN LETTERS, 1950
      pamplet let's speek out, Government-business interests, korean crises.
    - LOS NEGELES HARBOR, 1945 '44
  - GENERAL file by SUBJECTS, 1945-1947
    Arranged aphabetically in folders
    - Agriculture - soil conservation (district maps, directors lists, Calif. Stat soil conversation districts Act), 1945 (Box Box 65)
    - Alcoholic Industry (grain quotas), 1946
    - Aluminium Industry (Government owned aluminium plants in L A earas), 1945, '46
    - Argos, Greece (Rebuilding of city of Argos), 1945
    - Atomic Energy S 1717, 1946
    - British Loan, for... (Clippings Anglo-Amercan Financial Agreement), 1946
    - Byrnes Curfew order, 1945
    - California's Dairies, 1946
    - California Poultry Industry (Post-war conversion program 1945-50)
    - California Wool Industry (long-term Amercan Wool production [UNK], 1945, '48 '47 1947
    - Congressional Agreements, gen. (Pacific Coast Board of intergovernemental relations, 1945 1946
    - Dams, Flood control etc. H R 6591 Public Law 773, 1945-'46
    - Education H R 4929 1296 (Pamplet Education's mighty force, 1945, '46 1945)
    - Fishery Industry H R 3719 3837 3839 3844 3914 3928 4222 (Tuna fisheries North [UNK] Pacific), 1945
    - Foreign Interest Organisations H R 6780, 1945, '46
    - Gerald L K Smith Inc., 1945
    - Goverement Employers Compensation cases, 1946
    - Government control of corporations H R 2177, 1945
    - Hawaii Affairs, 1945
    - Hollywood Victory Committee (comm. activities pamplet), 1945
    - Hode (Civilian Production Adm.), 1946
    - Housing H R 1827 S 610 (Exhibits war housing, Welfare Council of metropolitan aera), Jan- July 1945
    - Housing S B 1342 (Report rent control practices etc county L A temporary shelter acts, surplus property act F H A), Aug.-Dec. 1945
    - Japanese Affairs., 1945, '46
    - [UNK] Steel - Fontana, 1945
    - Legislative Council Corr. H R 1296, 1945
    - Live Stock (cattle, sheep etc), 1945
    - Los Angeles Airports (proposed air terminal facilities L A airport 1944), 1945
    - Los Angeles Benefits (Federal Work [UNK] 1946), 1945
    - Los Angeles Board of Supervisors, 1945
    - Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce H J RES225 (Tax collections in California 1935-45 *Federal State, Local, Agriculture Committee of L A Chamber o Commerce), 1945
    - Los Angeles County Congressional Delegation, 1946, '47
    - Lumber Industry (lumber exports facts O P A), 1945, '46
    - McDonough Record (legisl. record 1933-44, L A Board of Supervisors), 1945
    - Maritime Commission Cases, 1947
    - Motion Pictures [UNK], 1945
    - Motion Pictures [UNK] Strike, 1945
    - National Debt data etc, 1945
    - Naval Examinations papers (Officers qualifications tests, candidates for [UNK]), 1945-48
    - Navy Department Discharges, 1945
    - Navy Department Discharges, 1946
    - Navy Department-Information (Navy demobilation), 1945
    - Navy Department-Special Data (Contractors lists, NavPers 15, 118), 1945
    - Negro Problems, 1945, '46
    - Newspapers, general, 1945
    - Nut Industry, 1945
    - O P A - Textile Industry (Office of Price Adm.), 1945
    - Overseas Problems, Military (reducing rations of soldiers in Europa), 1945
    - Petroleum Petroleum Administrator for war, 1944, '45 '47
    - Philippine Affairs, 1945, '46
    - Polish Affairs, 1946
    - Post Office Dept, Miscl., 1945
    - Pottery Industry, 1946
    - Public Employment Service, Fed. State, 1945
    - Reclamation Projects (National Reclamation Association), 1946
    - Religious discrimination, 1945
    - Rice Industry, 1945, '46
    - Rubber, 1945
    - Southern California Women's Republic Club, 1945
    - Transportation, 1945, '46
    - Treaty of peace with Italy (maps-boxed)
    - T V A H R 1824 (valley authoritorities in U S)
    - Yougoslavia, 1946
    - Letters on Army appointments (lists)
  - GENERAL file of SUBJECTS, 1947-1949
    Arranged alphabetically in folders with headers
    - Aircraft Industry, 1947, '45 '46 (Box Box 66)
    - California Affairs H R 3866 5952 5929 SRE 30 39 S J R 2 3 12 13 15 S 33 2189 2349 A J R I 2x 3 4 7 9 10 11 (Pacific Marine Review issue April [UNK]), 1948
    - California Agriculture, 1947
    - California Labor, 1947
    - Californai Live Stock, 1947
    - California Nut Industry (Edible tree nuts booklet, '46, View of U S tree Nut industry), 1947 '48
    - California Newspaper Problems, 1947 '48
    - California Steel Industry (Fontana etc), report on S RES 129 (War plants disposal, 1947 '46 '48
    - California Tidelands S 3 1988, 1947-48
    - Catholic Charities, 1947
    - Colorado River Problems S 1175 483 PB 1175 HJR 225 S J RES 145 HR 4097, 1947 '46
    - Colorado River Association (booklets: California Colorado river '48 California's Stake in the Colorado River), 1947
    - Congressional Calender, 1947
    - Congressional Directory, 1947
    - Congressional Record list, 1947 '48
    - Crank letters, 1947 '46
    - Dairy Industry, 1947 '46
    - Federal Employee Problems, 1947
    - Federal Employment Benefits HR 3232, 1947
    - Register List, 1947
    - Works Agency Public Law 697, 1947 '45
    - Works Agency Project Public Law 697, 1947
    - Fishing Industry, 1947 '48
    - Grain speculation, 1947 '48
    - Greek Loan Hold H R 99 (Greek-Turkish Loan), 1947 '46
    - Hollywood Womens Club Officers, 1947
    - Indian Affair, 1947 '48
    - Japanese Amercans, 1947
    - Jewish Affairs (Congressional record no 80 v 96 '50, the Nation vol 166 '48, record on partition), 1948 '49 '50
    - Kellog Arabian Farm, 1948
    - Labor Committee Hollywood Strike, 1948
    - Long Beach Affairs S J RES 145 226, 1947 '48
    - Los Angeles City Affairs, 1946 '47
    - Los Angeles County Affairs Public Law 697, 1946 '47 '48
    - Board of Supervisors
    - Housing, Basilone H R 2780 report 274 80 Congress I Sess, 1947
    - Housing Authority, 1947 '48
    - Shipyard Industry, 1948
    - Water Supply Company, 1948
    - Memorando
    - Merchant Marine H R 2633, 1946 '45 '46 '47
    - Mining Industry, 1947
    - Motion Picture Industry H J RES 140 (Brittish fim quota), 1947-49
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1947 '48
    - Nautical Affairs (compettion Navy engaged in commercial entreprises '46, N R O T C candidates list '48, 1947 '48
    - Newsprint, 1947
    - Panama Canal, 1947
    - Postal Affairs, 1947
    - Puerto Rico, 1947
    - Philippine Affairs Public Law 373, 1947
    - Red Cross (facts on R C services US Army), 1947
    - Statistics (census reports '45), 1947
    - Stone Industry, 1947
    - Warren for President, 1947
  - GENERAL file by SUBJECT, 1947-1954
    Arr. in folders with headings
    Arr. alphabetically by heading A thr. Y
    - AGAINST RECIPROCAL TRADE AGREEMENT ACT 1958 (Box Box 67)
    - AGAINST TITO Members of Congress protests, newspaper clippings, opposition to visit letters, Pres. Eisenhower proposal to invite Tito, Sen Kuchel 's letters, 1957
    - FOR RECIPROCAL TRADE AGEEMENT ACT 1958
      Administration's mutuak security program, extension of R T A, ply wood industry imports HR 10368 10818 12591
    - IN FAVOR OF TITO Catholic opposition, Dante Pavelic
    - PEASANT UNION International Peasant union,organization of Central eastr European parties in exile., 1959
    - PETROLEUM INDUSTRY oil shale, 1949
    - P T A GENERAL lobbying activities, 1953
    - PUBLICATIONS RECEIVED Banking legislation,Bill Graham, farm rural americans,national Grange address, R D activities (Mili tary research development) Tele education. -, 1957
    - PUBLICATIONS RECEIVED, 1959 '60
      California freeway expressway system,federal national mortgage association, Jewish calendar armed forces, journalism week University of Missouri,N R E C A, public housing, zirconium tubes for nuclear reactors.
    - same, 1961
      California state publications listing, Cinema education guild report '61,documentations of u n plots for takeover U.S.,economis activities analyses, Ford Motor Co,. participation in national defense space efforts, 48 national foreign trade convention, water C W special [UNK]
    - PUERTO-RICO AFFAIRS, 1948 '54
      Public Law 362 Puerto [UNK] Res 10 Elections of Governer, nationalists attack on U S congress men.
    - QUESTIONAIRE FOLDER Reactions to questionaires, 1961
    - RED CROSS Facts about services to Armed Forces., 1955 '61
    - R E A COMPANY Automatic control reseach development manufac ture., 1953
    - RESEARCH MATERIAL, 1957
      Chamber of Commerce U S business actions '51,control costs (government), economic outlook '51, European Review A continental communit, industry de-centralization plan for [UNK]
    - RUBBER INDUSTRY, 1950
      Prevention of rubber emergency
    - RUSSIAN AFFAIRS, 1957
      GrandDuke Vladimir of Russia, United [UNK] maonarchist organizations.
    - SLOVANIAN AFFAIRS, 1955 '59
      Platform [UNK] leage of America, Slovak national council abroad.
    - SMALL BUSINESS LIST CORRESPONDANCE Comprise on tariff legislation,products lists circular '55,Small Business Administration., 1955
    - SPACE DEBATE MATERIAL, 1958
      Declaration of policy purpose
    - SPACE FLIGHT, 1958
      Auxiliary power,communications, guidance stabilization manned orbital flight, manned un-Manned lunar landing, manned space stations,planetary probes, lunar probes, life support systems, reconnaisance satellites, [UNK] cic satellites, space time table Propusion, technilogical development,next decade missions.
    - SPEECH MATERIAL, 1954
      Action on floor amenmemts in House to apprpriations bills 83 Congr. 1 st Session, administrative achievements of Eisenhower by departments 1953-'54, atomic power for peace Eisenhower address, Baruch lectures riddle of self government making economic weather the dominant yearning, committee on government operations: activities accomplishments, communists propaganda,facts on postal pay raise veto-HR 6052 7774 9245 9836,general speech on why Republican 84 [UNK] is essential,government reorganizations plan 1 thr 10, HealthEducation Welfare HR 8149 2832, housing, inflation, monetray policy's new look (Amercan Bankers Ass.),national defence, postal service, social security, State of the Union Eisehower addres taxes, Agriculture Hj RES 355,President's [UNK] of Union addres President's message: the White House,republican federal [UNK] highway bill,review legislation 83 Congress, strategy tactics of world communism hearings 83 Congress.
    - SPIRITUAL MOBILIZATION
      Federal subsidies,religious liberty
    - TAYLOR FILE Disloyalty to US,F B I, clarification of status Marine Corps letters. letters to McDonough, Marine Corps-Police force., 1947
    - U Y, thr.
    - UKRANIAN AFFAIRS Anniversary independance of Ukraine in Congress,celebration communist take-over occupation of Ukraine,Ukrian congress committee of America, booklet: in questoof freedom, 1941, 1918-'58
    - UN-AMERICAN ORGANIZATIONS, 1957
      Women for legislative action, Women's international leage for peace freedom.
    - UN-INDENTIFIED HR 207, 1961,'62
      House on un-american activities, merchant marinefisheries committee, packing of Rules Committee, pay increase postal [UNK]
    - U S CAPITOL AFFAIRS
      Newspaper clippongs, Senate Office Building subway to Capitol costs.
    - U S CUSTOM HOUSE FEDERAL OFFICE BUILDING, 1959, '60
      Publiclaw 519, General Service Administration.
    - same facilities in harbor area, newspaper clippings,location in downtown civic center, 1961
    - U S ENTREPRISE [UNK] CARRIER, 1958
    - VETERANS ORGANIZATIONS, 1957 thr '62 1948 thr 1952
      Disabled american veterans, American Legion, AMVETS, LA Veteran Service Center,82nd Airborne division.
    - WESTERN UNION FILE file of telegrams sent/received
    - THE WESTERN WEB Index 1 80 Congr. 81 Congr. 82 Congr., thr. 3 1947-48 1949-50 1951-52
    - WESTERN WEB vol 1 chronlogical narrative Central Arizona Project, 1947-48
    - 2 narrative Central Arizona Project, 1949-50
    - 2 narrative Central Arizona Project, 1951-52
    - WHITE HOUSE CONFERENCE ON EDUCATION newsletters, 1955
    - WILLIAM, MAJOR Discharge, Williams Intelligence Summary, 1951 Aug.'51
    - YOGOSLAVIAN AFFAIRS Booklet: The truth about Croatia., 1957 '61; (folder)
    - same Newspaper clippings,McDonough protest letter,petition to President by congress men, Toto's visit to U S, 1956 '57; (envelop)
- PERSONAL PERSONAL POLITICAL SPECIAL POLITICAL file, 1947-1961
  boxes labelled P PP SP in box sequence I thr. 6 box lists arr. in folders enveloppes (not arr. in strict chronological or alphabetical sequence.)
  box 72 contains P P for 1962.
  - POLITICAL PERSONAL CORRESPONDANCE file, 1944 thr. 1954
    Arr. by year time period (letters in folio's not strictly in chronological arrangement, but to some extent groupe together by written in heading on [UNK] f. Personal Jan. - 48 are December '47 letters)
    - PERSONAL CORRESPONDANCE (Box P 68)
      - 1944 thr. 1945
      - 1946
      - 1946 July thr. 1947
      - 1947 Jan. thr. September
      - 1947 Augst thr. December
      - 1948 Jan.-
      - 1948 March thr. June
      - 1948 July thr. December
      - 1948 Jan. thr. December
      - 1949 February thr. May
      - 1949 June thr.November
      - 1949 December thr. June 1950
      - 1950 July thr. December
      - 1951 Jan. thr. June
      - 1951 July-
      - 1952 July thr. August
      - 1953 January thr. March
      - 1953 April thr. June
      - 1953 July thr. December
      - 1954 March thr. June
      - 1954 July-
  - PERSONAL POLITICAL CORRESPONDANCE file, 1947 thr 1953
    letters in folders with heading
    leetrs in folder chronilogicaaly arranged- so some extent only
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1947 March thr. December; folder A (Box PP 69)
    - August thr. December, folder B
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1948 January thr. May; folder C
    - February thr. July, folder D
    - June thr. December, folder E
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1949 January thr. February; folder F
    - February thr. August, folder G
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1950 June thr. December; folder H
    - January thr. July, folder I
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1951 April thr. December; folder J
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1952 January thr. June; folder K
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1953 January thr. March; folder L
    - July thr. December, folder M
  - PERSONAL POLITICAL CORRESPONDANCE file, 1954 thr. 1960
    letters in folio's with heading
    letters in folio's chronological arrangement - to some extent only
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1954 February thr. June; folio A (Box PP 70)
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1954 January thr June; folio B
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1954 June thr. December; C
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1954 January thr. Febreuary; D
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1955 January thr. May; E
    - I am the United States (Congressional Record copies), 1959; F
    - MC DONOUGH REMARKS (Congressional Record copies), 1960; G
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1955
  - PERSONAL POLITICAL CORRESPONDANCE file 1956, thr. 1958
    letters in folders enveloppes with headings
    letters in enveloppes folders chronologically arranged- to some extent
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, Jan.-1956 (Box PP 71)
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, March -1957
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, August- 1957
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1958
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, Jan.-1958
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, Jan.-1958
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, July-1958
    - SPECIAL POLITICAL, 1959-1960
    - PERSONAL (Correspondance)
    - 1957 January thr. October
    - 1958 Jan.-
    - 1959 Jan. thr. October
    - 1960 Jan.-
  - PERSONAL PERSONAL POLITICAL SPECIAL POLITICAL [UNK] file, 1957 thr. 1962
    folders in box arr. by year/part of year
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1957 January- (Box P SP 72)
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1961 May-
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1961 May-
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1961 May-
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1961 May-
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1962
    - PERONAL POLITICAL, 1962 January-
    - SPECIAL POLITICAL, 1955/56
  - PERSONAL POLITICAL CORRESPONDENCE file, 1959 thr. 1961
    folders in box arranged by year/part of year
    Correpondance not in alphabetical or chronilogical arrangement.
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1959 January- (Box PP 73)
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1959 January-
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1960 January-
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1960 May-
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1961 January-
    - PERSONAL POLITICAL, 1961 January-
- CORRESPONDENCE file OUT-GOING (yellow copies of letter)
  in boxes letters grouped by headers in 16 Boxes
  Arr. alphabetically by HEADING
  * Letters have headings in writing, such as f.i. Tax legislation, Campaign '58 favor, Internal Revenue case. These have not been put together per group by originators of the files.
- Miscellaneous
  Materials arranged in 13 boxs labelled 1 thr. 13 (boxes 90 thr. 102). Box labels indicate time period of meterials, method of arrangement of contents which is by original headings with correspondance, contents (in some cases), bills*, organisation(s)*, Subject(s)* which have been extracted from correspondance. The list of time-period of materials will be helpfull to approach these time-wise. Box labels have a yellow dot on left side lower corner for easy identification since boxes labels look alike. The dots are also on all sides of the boxes. A few headings in boxes 7 12 have not been analyzed because this would result in duplication of information already obtained (7) or the hadings (12) may need a seperate analyses of contents.
  - MISCELLANEOUS materials in folders albums, 1920-1944
    Arr. alphabetically according to HEADING
    - A PAPERS, clippings (newspapers), 1944 (Box 90)
    - CANDIDATES FOR MAYOR Buron Fitts, John [UNK] Ford, Rheba Crawford, Shaw. Newspaperclippings, 1937 '35
    - EXAMINER clippings (newspapers), 1944
    - HERALD EXPRESS clippings (newspapers), 1944
    - ILLEGIBLE FOLDER clippings (newspapers) Postau Case, 1939
    - LABOR PAPERS clippings (newspapers), 1944
    - McDONOUGH NITRO STARCH EXPERIMENTS, 1917, 16
    - NEWS clippings (newspapers), 1944
    - SCRAP BOOK clippings (newspapers), 1937
    - TIMES clippings (newspapers), 1944
    - UN-MARKED ALBUM clippings, cards etc., 1920-29
    - UN-MARKED FOLDER miscellaneous transcripts of proceedins a.o., 1935-43
    - CHRISMAS LIST, 1933-35 (Box 91)
    - FLANNERY Newspaper clippings, 1950
    - KNIGHTS OF COLUMBUSI Cabrillo Assemby, commemorating Columbus Day '36, Diocese of L A San Diego, directory Cabrillo Assembly 4th degree, 8 12 official programs '32 '35, Fourth degree exemtifications '35, Holy Name Union, Manchester Heights exposition '26, national [UNK] of Catholic cherities, proceedings District Assemby 4th degree knights, Sierra pilgrimage Carmel Mission 1927. American association for recognition of Irish [UNK] Saint Vicent de Paul society., 1924-29
    - LEGISLATIVE RECORD Sen MC DOUGH
      2 District L A count Board of Supervisors 1934-1944 complete listing
    - NEWSPAPER PUBLICITY, 1950
      Campaign clippings
    - PERSONAL (see folder), 1933
    - PERSONAL (see folder), 1935
    - PERSONAL (see folder), 1937 '36
    - PERSONAL RECEIPTS, 1921-'44
    - THANKS, 1934
    - McDONOUGH College notes, 1942-43
    - [UNK]
      (not analysed)
    - NEW CITIZENS LIST, 1961 April- May
    - VOTE TABULATION not on IBM of election Assembly Districts, Nov. '54 58 63 65
    - PHOTOGRAPHS, CUTS MATS of Mc D. parties
    - PERSONAL, 1936
      Christmas cards lists, list of election deputees for organisations, personal letters, personal addresses of officials, religious persecution in Mexico, road oil Gilmore Oil Company, wedding invitations lists.
  - MISCELLANEOUS materials in folders maps, 1933-1944
    Arr. alphabetically by HEADING, not analyzed for subject(s), bills organization(s)
    - CAMPAIGN Newspapers clppings, 1940 (Box 92)
    - CAMPAIGN Newspapers clppings, 1941 '40
    - CAMPAIGN Newspapers clppings, 1942 '43
    - G L McDOUNOUGH Newspapers clppings, 1944
    - GENERAL ELECTION RETURNS Primary final per precints, 1937
    - L A TIBUNE STORY Ventura Property Owners Association, 1943 '39
    - LISTS oF DEPUTEES supervisoral didtrict, 2 Jun/July 1932
    - NEWS RELEASES Circulars from McDonough campaign headquerters, 1944
    - POLITICAL MATTERS correspondance, 1933
    - POLITICAL MATTERS correspondance, 1934
    - POLITICAL MATTERS correspondance, 1936
    - POLITICAL, 1942
    - PRIMARY ELECTION RETURNS tabulations precints 14 thr570, 1934